Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
rge ahead, painting
Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
What's going on?! I thought we caught the thunder one!
You've got some nerve, Kid!
You will pay a steep price..
...for sending me to the depths!
Better get ready!
What now?
We're in for a bad time.
Energetic old hag, for sure. What's more...
...don't it seem like' she's even more powerful?
Holy crap... Think we'd better...
..get the hell outta here!
Oh, no you don't!
And now, time to test out your skills!
Show me what you've got!
Okay, Mama!
Fulgora!
* Was it just me, or was there a huge freaking bang just now?
Killer...
Ya there?
Uh-huh...
Dammit! She really sent us packin'.
An Emperor of the Sea's power is really something else.
One thing's for sure... The hag's freakin' insane.
Anyway, where the hell are we?
Several floors down in the castle, I guess.
What about Big Mom?
Not coming after us.
The hole she made is so big, she must've lost track of where she sent us flying.
Kid!
Where are you?!
I'm gonna murder the crap out of you!
Kinda looks like she's down there...
I'm gonna make sure the ol' prune doesn't team back up with Kaido again!
I'm sendin' her straight to hell! Let's get moving!
M I'm sending anybody that laughs at you straight to hell!
Straw Sword!
You...
66 hagitianBasidSawkins Hawkins!
"Magician"Basil Sawkins Worst Generation- Animal Kingdom Pirates Seadliner
You son of a...
Big mistake to come here and take jabs at us.
Double-crosser!
I was betrayed by Apoo, much like you.
I was simply avoiding a fight I knew I would lose!
Hard to believe the lot of you survived this long.
Kid, go on without me.
Can't leave Big Mom on the loose.
This guy's...
...my problem now.
All yours, bud!
Kid's getting away! After him!
Thank you...
Two against one would have been unfavorable odds.
Demon Conqueror's Countenance!
Hell of a job you're doing as one of the Animal Kingdom Pirates' Headliners.
Even got you totally house-trained.
E Say what you will.
There's a 92 percent chance you die here.
How unfortunate, Kamazo the Slasher!
Again with the fortune-telling? Well, fortune favors the bold!
I wish you luck, Killer.
Screw your luck.
I ain't wishin' you...
...even the tiniest bit of luck.
Have you morons ever thought about giving up?!
The dino dude's actually hitching a ride!
Get out of here!
11 FUsopp! Go for the vitals!
Already on it!
We're not quitters! And we never say die!
Temple!
Chin!
Adam's apple!
Why, ya dirty little
Give it up, ya scaly freak show!
Eyeball!
Nostril!
Would you just fall off already?!
How many times do we gotta hit ya before ya let go?!
How tough can ya freakin' be?!
0.
You can do it, Komachiyo! Just a little further, now!
If we can get to the stage on the Performance Floor,
I can give orders to the bad guys that Horselina-chan and her creW..
...force-fed my Kibi Dango!
And if they come to our side..
...have done my part!
If I can be helpful to everybody...
I dun care what happens to me!
11//
So get us to the stage!
Don't say crap like that, Tama!
Get a grip!
The fight's not over 'til we've taken back Wano!
O-Tama! Hang in there!
This young lady and old man'll make sure you stay safe and sound!
Hey, who you callin' an "old man?!" I'm only nineteen, dammit!
Just like Big Bro Luffy,
all I wanted to do was help everyone!
But I's...
...I's scared and I can't take it anymore...
Even with the Gifters on your side, you still don't got a chance!
Don't push your luck, brat!
The kid's already scared outta her mind!
Sorry, Tama.
Your anxiety's a thing of the past!
Leave this to me!
Usopp!
Hope ya got clean underwear on, you mutant lizard!
Ugly-ass nose troll!
Everything you do pisses me off!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Whaaa?! What the hell did you and your ridiculous nose do to me?!
Firework Flowers!
So hot!
Come on now, Usopp!
1 Sorry!
1 I don't have a lot of  close-range ammo!
Anyway, time to put him down for good!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Exploding Pinecones!
For real, Usopp!
Hell yeah! Direct hit!
How 'bout dem apples, freak show?!
Scratch one lizard!
You...
S Youl...
You son of a..!
He got back up again!
What the hell is with these prehistoric freaks of nature?!
Dammit...
Freakin' long-nosed jackass!
What I wouldn't give for Kibi Dango to work on him...
They only work on Smile users! What do we do if he comes back?!
O For now, let's get to the Performance Floor ASAP!
We need to see O-Tama's plan through!
Huh? I'm free...
Where's Mama?
Mama! Where are you?!
I'll be right there, Mama!
Mama, where are you?! Answer me! I wanna help!
Eustasser lost a lot of strength...
And Big Mom's gone back to the castle...
If she comes back for that thundercloud, we're in for a bad time.
Hey!
I'm leaving you here and taking everybody else!
Gotcha!
Mama!
Whuh?
Tell everybody for me...
...I said that!
Somebody's having fun!
AVIN
The greater the danger, the wider your smile, and the wider your smile... Is that it?
1/1
Luffy!
I beg of you... Defeat him!
Kaido!
That little brat!
Repel!
Come on out, Kid!
What?!
Big Mom?!
It's you dolts!
*/
Why..?!
It's you dolts!
The Cat Burglar... And the one with the long nose...
We are so dead!
Straw Hat's crew, eh...
0 O-Lin-chan!
O-Tama?!
It's been a while!
Oh,if it isn't O-Tama!
So glad to see you again!
Whatever brings you to a dangerous place like this?
What the hell?!
I've never seen Big Mom like that!
I's been worried about you, O-Lin-chan!
Ya just up and left Udon outta the blue!
Uh-huh! Thank you for taking care of me when I lost my memory!
Good for you! Yer memory's come back then?
Mm-hmm!
This is really bad...
She's gone into Mother Mode... This happens every once in a while with kids under ten!
Hol-ho-hooold on, O-Tama!
You're friends with her?!
Your kimono really looks good on ya!
You think SO?!
The hairpin's brand new!
O-Tama! Shoo her away!
Say, the person that did my hair..
That busybody of a poor woman from Okobore Town...
Oh, O-Tsuru! How's she been?
I'll never forget how that little drop of oshiruko tasted!
It was so delicious!
I'd love to have some again..
O Thing is... O-Lin-chan..
The Okobore Town ya knew is gone.
"Gone?" What do you mean by that?
After we left for Udon,
Okobore Town got attacked!
We burned the mountain bandits' mountain to the ground!
But instead of seeking revenge,
they keep stealing tons of food from our farm!
You lot got anything to do with it?
W-We know nothing!
I heard the samurai are preparing for a raid... Could that be why?
If so, we can't let them know!
What's with all the whispering?!
I will guide you!
I only ask that you do not hurt anyone!
O... O-Tsuru-san!
Guide me?
You know something about this, then?
You will see once you get there. It is a little far though...
No, O-Tsuru-san! You don't have to cover for us!
It's fine! All we wanted was to eat our fill before we died!
So you're the culprits, then!
The villagers lied about bein' the ones that ate the food' 'fore the raid,
..when it was actually the samurai 'n their folk that ate it.
So the guys workin' for Kaido..
...burned down the town!
Huh?
O-Lin-san!
They're rebels! Don't let them get away!
Burn 'em down with their houses!
This is oshiruko. Go on, O-Lin-san, try it!
So good!
It's delicious!
Okobore Town?!
Oh, you're looking great, O-Lin-san! O
am?
That's so cute!
I want my hair done like you two!
I will tend to your hair once you are a little older.
Ya will!
I'll help out, too!
My, how astonishing!
O-Lin-san, you look beautiful!
Looks good on you!
Thank you all!
So people working under Kaido killed them...
It's the death penalty for this town!
Burn it to ash!
The people that helped me when I lost my memory...
O-Lin-san!
All those people...
All those people in Okobore Town that were so kind to me...
You're telling me they were all done in?!
Here comes the dino dude!
O-Lin-chan! One o' Kaido's guys is attacking us!
Kaido?
Go away! We're in the middle of something!
Go on, keep howling 'til you drop dead!
Get us outta here, Komachiyo!
Hey, Big Mom!
Don't let 'em past you!
Go, Komachiyo!
You're not going anywhere!
Too slow! You're done!
/1
Shut up!
Don't you know...
...that even in the cruel world of piracy...
...there's still a code of honor?!
=: :
Damn youuuu!
You clowns!
Big Sis!
Over that way.. Big Mom!
That's Mama! Great! She's alive!
You okay, Komachiyo?!
You gotta get up!
CUNTINUED